BRILIANTO AZHARI SUPRAPTO

 $briliantosuprapto 18@\,gmail.com \mid (+62)\ 82115146886 \mid https://www.linkedin.com/in/briliantosuprapto-14a3a51b4/$

PROFILE

Informatics Engineering students at the Jakarta State Polytechnic gain experience in working on projects and are interested in developing innovative and effective technology through programming in the field of Information Technology and Computers. Has several abilities such as programming with JavaScript, PHP. Project Management such as requirements analysis, design, implementation and testing. Database with CRUD operations. Furthermore, they have skills in communication, teamwork, high motivation, creative and innovative and easy to adapt to new environments. Want to develop skills like Frontend and Backend Developer, Web Developer as well as Software Developer.

EDUCATION

(D4) (Informatics Engineering), (Jakarta State Polytechnic)

2020 - 2024

• GPA: 3.58 / 4.00

(D2) (Software Engineer), (CEP-CCIT FT Universitas Indonesia)

2020 - 2022

• GPA: 3.57 / 4.00

EXPERIENCES

(Intern) Frontend Web Developer –Web Based Employee Assignment Management Application (Department of Communication and Informatics of Bogor Regency) 2023/08 – 2024/02

- Responsible for developing a web-based system for the assignment management system.
- The application is made using the next is programming language.
- Performing Frontend Work on the System Management section for Assignment Features, approval, taking data, receiving data, sending files.
- Perform Backend Work using API in Go Lang programming language

(Project) Backend Developer – Consumables System in the Workshop (Jakarta State Polytechnic) 2023/03 – 2023/06

- Responsible for developing a web-based system for the Consumables System in the Workshop
- Performing Frontend Work on the Management System for Goods Location Storage Features using PHP with the Laravel Framework. And creating CRUD functions on the Goods Location section in Buildings, Warehouses, Blocks and Locations
- Performing Backend Work on the Item Location Storage Feature System Management section such as integrating code, setting URL endpoints and directing certain functions in the system.

(Project) Backend Developer – Games Corner (CCIT FTUI)

2022/06 - 2022/07

- Responsible for developing a web and mobile-based system on the Games Corner application that contains news, content, information on a game from year to year. And has a feature to rent the games.
- Perform Backend Work on the Game Purchase/Rental Form section using PHP, JavaScript for the Website and using the Dart language with the Flutter Framework for the Mobile App version. As well as creating CRUD functions for the web and mobile versions in the Login Page section for Admin and User, as well as on the Purchase/Rental Form.
- Collaborate with my Project Friend who is a Frontend Developer to maximize their time for communication and teamwork to be able to complete this project well.

CERTIFICATES

 LSP ICT Competency Test Certification BNSP – Software Development Course Certificate – Huawei HCIA-AI V 3.0 Course 	2024 2024
Certificate English Competency Test – TOEIC	2024
 Participating in Senior Web Design at Itechno Cup 2022 	2022
• Certificate Intern in Department of Communication and Informatics of Bogor Regency	2023
• Certificate Project Consumables System in the Workshop at Jakarta State Polytechnic	2023
Professional Certificate in Information Technology CEP CCIT-FTUI	2022
• Certificate English Competency Test – TOEFL	2022
HTML5 Programming	2021
Object Oriented Programming (OOP)	2021

SKILLS

Hard Skills: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, PHP (CodeIgniter & Laravel), Next.JS, Node.Js, Web Application, Frontend Development, API, JavaScript Programming, UI/UX, Database (MySQL).

Soft Skills : Communication skills, good teamwork, highly motivated and easy to adapt to new environments .